<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="main_string">Chào mừng bạn sử dụng AA AIO Tweaker\n
Đây là ứng dụng sẽ giúp bạn tinh chỉnh một vài thông số trong Android Auto\n
Chỉ đơn giản là chọn và điều chỉnh các thông số mà bạn muốn :)\n
Nếu bạn chưa chắc chắn gì những gì công cụ sẽ làm, chỉ cần ấn giữ và bảng hướng dẫn sẽ hiện ra.\n</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Chọn ứng dụng</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_shortcuts">Lối tắt đến lệnh</string>
    <string name="patch_custom_apps">ứng dụng ngoài</string>
    <string name="disable_speed_limitations">giới hạn số lần chạm</string>
    <string name="unlimited_scrolling_when_driving">giới hạn tốc độ</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_animation_in_navbar">Biểu tượng trợ lý trên thanh điều hướng</string>
    <string name="splash">Ứng dụng này có thể thay đổi một vài thông số của Android Auto và bỏ qua một số tính năng an toàn mà Google đã tích hợp trong Android Auto.\n
Khi sử dụng ứng dụng này, bạn đồng ý với BẠN, và CHỈ MÌNH BẠN sẽ chịu trách nhiệm với những vấn đề có thể xảy ra khi thay đổi các tính năng an toàn như thương tật, thiệt hại tài sản, mất mạng.\n
Trong mọi trường hợp, tác giả của ứng dụng này không chịu trách nhiệm về việc bạn sử dụng nó</string>
    <string name="proceed">Tôi hiểu</string>
    <string name="navigation_at_start">Điều hướng khi khởi động</string>
    <string name="statb_opaque_string">Buộc thanh trạng thái tối</string>
    <string name="battery_outline_string">biểu tượng tiết kiệm pin</string>
    <string name="legend">Biểu tượng trạng thái:\n
XANH LÁ CÂY: Đã áp dụng thay đổi\n
VÀNG: Cần khởi động lại để áp dụng\n
ĐỎ: Thay đổi chưa được áp dụng</string>
    <string name="set_notification_duration_to">Thời lượng thông báo đến</string>
    <string name="base_no_ws">Màn hình dài</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_text">Ép thành màn hình dài</string>
    <string name="media_notification_duration_to">Thời lượng thông báo tên bài hát đến</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_auto_connect">Tự động kết nối Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nospeed">Công cụ này sẽ làm làm Android Auto nghĩ rằng xe của bạn đang không di chuyển. Với điều này, Android Auto sẽ luôn luôn hiển thị mục xem trước nội dung tin nhắn. Công cụ này sẽ không hiển thị cho bàn phím trên Android Auto.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sixtap">This tweak will override the 6 tap limit of Android Auto and will make unlimited browsing of content always possible.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_shortcuts">This tweak will unlock the new Assistant Shortcuts feature. Once activated you can go in Android Auto settings, and in the customize launcher
    section you can start adding shortcuts to Google Assistant commands</string>
    <string name="tutorial_startup">This tweak will override the default behaviour of Android Auto opening a navigation app at start and will make Android Auto start on launcher.\n
        In some cases this tweak will disable auto start of music. A known workaround is to disable and re-enable the option within Android Auto settings.\n
    IT\'S NOT POSSIBLE TO SET A SPECIFIC APP TO START FIRST.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_widescreen">This tweak will force Android Auto in widescreen mode.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_no_widescreen">This tweak will force Android Auto in no widescreen mode.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_animation">This tweak enable an animation of Google Assistant in the navigation bar.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_statusbar_opaque">This tweak will make the status bar always black.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_outline">This tweak will prevent the battery icon with the red outline when battery saver is on.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_hun">This tweak let you set a custom duration for heads up notifications</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_hun">This tweak let you set a custom duration for media notifications in navigation bar to up to 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bluetooth">This tweak should prevent Bluetooth from turning on when Android Auto is connected. This tweak won\'t work if Bluetooth is already on.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_patchapps">This tweak will enable third-party apps made specifically with Android Auto custom SDK to work on Android Auto.\n
If you are familiar with AA Phenotype Patcher, this tweak is pretty much identical to it.\n
It\'s not possible to add just any app to Android Auto, but it\'s possible to patch sideloaded apps MADE FOR ANDROID AUTO to work in cars.</string>
    <string name="multi_display_string">Multi Display</string>
    <string name="tutorial_multidisplay">This is an hidden feature inside Android Auto that will turn the second space in widescreen mode to a real second display that is completely taken by a seond activity. Google Maps will display a full map with navigation status, music and phones will take the full space.\n
Additionally, this mode activates another feature that will turn the phone\'s screen in a second display for navigation in Android Auto.\n
Settings for tweaking this feature will be available in Android Auto homescreen.\n
Apparently, only Google Maps currently support this mode.\n
This feature is probably under development and could potentially not work as intended.\n
Android Auto 5.8 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="battery_warning">Battery saver warning</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_saver_warning">This tweak will prevent Android Auto from giving popup warnings when battery saver mode is on</string>
    <string name="disable_tweak_string">Disable\u0020</string>
    <string name="enable_tweak_string">Enable\u0020</string>
    <string name="re_enable_tweak_string">Re-enable\u0020</string>
    <string name="copy_log">Copy log</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="revert_everything">Revert everything</string>
    <string name="force_disable_tweak">Force Disable\u0020</string>
    <string name="reset_tweak">Reset\u0020</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_warning">Force widescreen has been automatically disabled</string>
    <string name="force_disable_widescreen_warning">Force disable widescreen has been automatically disabled</string>
    <string name="set_value">Set\u0020</string>
    <string name="reboot_to_apply">REBOOT TO APPLY</string>
    <string name="warning_title">WARNING</string>
    <string name="unpatch">Unpatch\u0020</string>
    <string name="patch_app">Patch\u0020</string>
    <string name="default_string">\u0020Default</string>
    <string name="app_list_label">Apps List</string>
    <string name="positive_button">ok</string>
    <string name="translators_button">Translated by</string>
    <string name="about_part_one"><![CDATA[AA AIO TWEAKER is developed and maintained by Shmykelsa.<br><br>Source code is available on <a href=\"https://github.com/shmykelsa/AA-Tweaker\">GitHub</a><br><br>]]></string>
    <string name="about_part_two"><![CDATA[If you really like my work, please consider a donation.<br> You can donate me through <a href=\"http://www.paypal.me/grizzo96\">PayPal</a> or you can copy my Bitcoin address with the button down below.<br><br>Even a small amount will be much appreciated :)]]></string>
    <string name="copied_address_toast">BTC Address copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="custom_wallpapers">Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="tutorial_wallpapers">This tweak will activate the new built in wallpaper changer in Android Auto. Android Auto 5.8 or superior is required.\nWARNING: If you are a user of Wallpapers For Android Auto, you will need to update it to at least version 3.0, otherwise this tweak will break Wallpapers For Android Auto functionality.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_dark_mode">Starting from December 2020, Google reverted a behaviour that happened since Android 10. Previously, the light/dark mode on Android Auto followed the light/dark mode on the phone and vice versa. This meant that switching the phone to dark mode had effect on the car, or if the phone was in dark mode and the car had lights off it used to switch on the light theme on the phone.\n However, since this feature of \"independent\" dark mode was introduced, users with Aftermarket headunits have no way to switch to dark mode anymore without actually wiring the stereo to the car\'s lights.\n This tweak makes sure that night mode is again dependent from phone and switching light/dark mode on phone will have its effects on cars too.</string>
    <string name="dark_mode_tweak">independent dark mode</string>
    <string name="telemetry_string">telemetry</string>
</resources>
