<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="main_string">Vítejte v AA AIO Tweakeru\n
        Tato aplikace Vám umožní použít některá vylepšení pro Android Auto\n
        Jednoduše zvolte, jaké vylepšení chcete použít :)\n
        Pokud si nejste jisti, co která možnost dělá, jejím dlouhým podržením se zobrazí návod.\n</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Výběr aplikací</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_shortcuts">Zkratky asistenta</string>
    <string name="patch_custom_apps">vlastní aplikace</string>
    <string name="disable_speed_limitations">omezení poklepání</string>
    <string name="unlimited_scrolling_when_driving">rychlostní omezení</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_animation_in_navbar">Animace asistenta v navigačním panelu</string>
    <string name="splash">Tato aplikace může změnit chování systému Android Auto a obejít některé bezpečnostní funkce, které Google implementoval v systému Android Auto.\n
        Používáním tohoto softwaru souhlasíte s tím, že na sebe přebíráte plnou zodpovědnost, za případné důsledky způsobené změnou ochranných prvků. Vystavujete se tedyriziku zranění sebe nebo
        jiných osob, poškození majetku, ztráty na životech.\n
        Autor této aplikace neni za žádných okolností zodpovědný za její používání</string>
    <string name="proceed">Rozumím</string>
    <string name="navigation_at_start">Navigace při startu</string>
    <string name="statb_opaque_string">Vynutit neprůhledný stavový panel</string>
    <string name="battery_outline_string">obrys spořiče baterie</string>
    <string name="legend">Legenda Stavů:\n
        ZELENÁ= Patch aplikován\n
        ŽLUTÁ= Patch vyžaduje restart aplikace\n
        ČERVENÁ= Patch není aplikován</string>
    <string name="set_notification_duration_to">Doba trvání oznámení do</string>
    <string name="base_no_ws">Širokoúhlá obrazovka</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_text">Vynutit širokoúhlý obraz</string>
    <string name="media_notification_duration_to">Doba trvání oznámení do</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_auto_connect">Automatické připojení Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nospeed">Toto vylepšení způsobí, že si Android Auto bude myslet, že vozidlo stojí na místě, tedy má nulovou rychlost. Což znamená, že Android Auto bude vždy
    zobrazovat náhledy zpráv. Toto vylepšení nijak nrovlivni klávesnici nebo prvotní nastavení. show the preview of messages.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sixtap">This tweak will override the 6 tap limit of Android Auto and will make unlimited browsing of content always possible.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_shortcuts">This tweak will unlock the new Assistant Shortcuts feature. Once activated you can go in Android Auto settings, and in the customize launcher
    section you can start adding shortcuts to Google Assistant commands</string>
    <string name="tutorial_startup">This tweak will override the default behaviour of Android Auto opening a navigation app at start and will make Android Auto start on launcher.\n
        This tweak could occasionally fail because sometimes Android Auto starts with a navigation to home or work autonomously. This behaviour breaks the tweak.\n
        In some cases this tweak will disable auto start of music. A known workaround is to disable and re-enable the option within Android Auto settings.\n
    IT\'S NOT POSSIBLE TO SET A SPECIFIC APP TO START FIRST.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_widescreen">This tweak will force Android Auto in widescreen mode.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_no_widescreen">This tweak will force Android Auto in no widescreen mode.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_animation">This tweak enable an animation of Google Assistant in the navigation bar.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_statusbar_opaque">This tweak will make the status bar always black.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_outline">This tweak will prevent the battery icon with the red outline when battery saver is on.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_hun">This tweak let you set a custom duration for heads up notifications</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_hun">This tweak let you set a custom duration for media notifications in navigation bar to up to 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bluetooth">BETA This tweak should prevent Bluetooth from turning on when Android Auto is connected. This tweak
    won\'t work if Bluetooth is already on, and currently it is in beta.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_patchapps">This tweak will enable third-party apps made specifically with Android Auto custom SDK to work on Android Auto.\n
        If you are familiar with AA Phenotype Patcher, this tweak is pretty much identical to it.\n
        It\'s not possible to add just any app to Android Auto, but it\'s possible to patch sideloaded apps MADE FOR ANDROID AUTO to work in cars.</string>
    <string name="multi_display_string">Multi Display</string>
    <string name="tutorial_multidisplay">This is an hidden feature inside Android Auto that will turn the second space in widescreen mode to a real second display that is completely taken by a seond activity. Google Maps will display a full map with navigation status, music and phones will take the full space.\n
        Additionally, this mode activates another feature that will turn the phone\'s screen in a second display for navigation in Android Auto.\n
        Settings for tweaking this feature will be available in Android Auto homescreen.\n
        Apparently, only Google Maps currently support this mode.\n
        This feature is probably under development and could potentially not work as intended.\n
    Android Auto 5.8 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="battery_warning">Battery saver warning</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_saver_warning">This tweak will prevent Android Auto from giving popup warnings when battery saver mode is on</string>
    <string name="disable_tweak_string">Disable\u0020</string>
    <string name="enable_tweak_string">Enable\u0020</string>
    <string name="re_enable_tweak_string">Re-enable\u0020</string>
    <string name="copy_log">Copy log</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="revert_everything">Revert everything</string>
    <string name="force_disable_tweak">Force Disable\u0020</string>
    <string name="reset_tweak">Reset\u0020</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_warning">Force widescreen has been automatically disabled</string>
    <string name="force_disable_widescreen_warning">Force disable widescreen has been automatically disabled</string>
    <string name="set_value">Set\u0020</string>
    <string name="reboot_to_apply">REBOOT TO APPLY</string>
    <string name="warning_title">WARNING</string>
    <string name="unpatch">Unpatch\u0020</string>
    <string name="patch_app">Patch\u0020</string>
    <string name="default_string">\u0020Default</string>
</resources>
